Good afternoon from Jakarta, Indonesia.
It's my first time to be here.
I am very excited.
I love Jakarta.
Well, we'll have to see about that because I've just arrived.
So we'll find out if I do indeed love Jakarta.
Now, we have a very special mission today.
We are heading to the National Monuments.
I'm going to take the Metro or the MRT, the subway.
I don't know what you call it.
I'm very new to Jakarta.
I don't know what you call anything.
I don't know the language.
I don't know anything.
So we're going to figure it out as we go.
Well, I can't even read that sign.
I can't read anything.
Oh, I can read that.
Block A. Right.
So we're heading into the Metro station now.
This is Afean station.
The streets are hustling and bustling and thriving with life.
This guy's selling some kind of drinks.
Right.
So we're heading in the station now.
And I don't know any, as I said, I'm fresh.
I'm fresh off the plane on the streets of Jakarta.
I don't even know how you pronounce Jakarta.
Should I pronounce it more like Jakarta or Jakarta?
Anyway, we're going in now.
Hello.
I see the National Monument.
Uh, what day am I?
Uh, yeah.
You want to buy a single trip or a multi-trip?
Single.
OK.
Thank you.
That's easier.
OK.
Yes.
Not from the way.
OK.
Thank you.
I have made it inside.
I have my ticket.
I have no idea.
Uh, what station he said.
I should get off at.
I just heard something.
He said Bondaran.
I think Bondaran.
Bondaran.
Wow.
This is, I'm experiencing everything for the first time.
These are the tracks of the MRT.
It looks quite clean and fresh.
I'm very excited.
I'm very excited to be here in Jakarta.
It's my first time.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm still being taken aback by everything.
Let me just calm down for a second.
Let me just sit down.
I'm getting, I'm getting, I'm getting too excited.
Oh, it has a little map on the ticket.
That's quite useful.
And it cost me 13,000.
I don't know what the money is called.
Uh, I do know.
Rupiah, Indonesian Rupiah.
It cost me 13,000 Indonesian Rupiah.
And, uh, just waiting for the train now.
The journey begins.
And here is the train.
All aboard, please, all aboard.
Let's head inside now to, to the National Monument.
I don't know how many stops this is going to be.
But we're going to figure this out as we go.
Well, it is very clean.
I wonder if you can, can you walk in between?
No, you can.
Oh.
Wow, it's absolutely in my fits on this train.
I better check, I better check out where am I going.
Let's check the map.
Hold on.
I just checked on my phone.
And he said it's going to take 50 minutes to get there.
And then when I clicked on the National Monument,
it said that it's closed today.
Today is a Monday.
Um, so, there's a slight bump in the, you know,
a slight road bump.
Anyway, I think we're going to go there.
Just take a look at it.
And then a new quest will appear.
Okay, so another kind of speed bump.
I was sat on the train.
And then I realized it started to go back in the direction
that I came from.
So now, so now I've just got off at a station.
I think I've got to change line.
The station doesn't, this line doesn't go all the way
to where I want to go.
So now I'm off the train.
And I've switched over to this side.
And I think I've got to go to Bendungan Hilir.
Bendungan Hilir.
I think that's where I'm going.
Oh, why is going off?
This is not a good start.
I should have prepared.
If you don't prepare, then prepare, prepare to fail.
But anyway, I must say this station is immaculate.
And there's kind of dancing, dancing Cheerio guys on the screens.
You know, there's no rubbish at all.
There's no kind of creepy guys hanging around
or feel completely safe.
Anyway, first impression so far.
Oh, Jakarta.
It's pretty good.
But the journey continues.
Like over here.
If this was the UK, there'd be a dude laid out on here.
Or it'd probably be living there.
This would be his little house.
It'd just be laid out on here.
I guess I'll just lay here waiting for the next train.
Back on the train.
We've acquired a new side mission.
And that mission is to walk down the train and look at people.
And I should talk quietly because I also don't want to annoy them on their journey.
I like these little doors, are they?
You can just go through.
Walk around.
I think on the London underground,
you can't walk between the passengers whilst it's moving.
I also know that we have these kind of doors.
Security guys walking on the train.
So I wonder if there is any kind of criminal activity on the train.
I mean, it seems pretty safe.
I wonder if there's two stop beggars coming on the train.
That's the only thing I can think of.
If you guys know, let me know in the comments below.
Why do they have the security guys?
Right, I decided to get off the train.
Just need to get outside and get our bearings.
Is that okay?
You can tell how safe a country is when on the gates to the Metro there's no actual barrier.
To stop you from sneaking in.
It's just wide open. There's no barrier.
So, guessing Jakarta is pretty safe, right?
Let's just head outside. Is this the way outside?
Let's just get outside and see where we are and check Google Maps.
I don't know where I've come to.
I think I'm at some... I think I'm at...
I don't know where I am.
Let's just look outside.
It seems I've got off at some kind of central business district.
Look at this skyscraper. That one kind of reminds me of the skyscraper in Bangkok.
That's very similar.
And the famous Jakarta traffic is in full effect.
And I've heard a lot about the air in Jakarta.
People are saying that it's very polluted.
But so far, I don't know.
It doesn't seem too bad.
But we'll find out. Maybe tomorrow.
I've got a sore throat.
I'm just being careful on the cross in the road.
Kapinski hotel over there.
Oh, there's a guy taking a picture.
Taking a picture of a lot of shore.
There's the Grand Hyatt hotel over there as well.
It's quite an expensive hotel.
I am staying in the Femont Jakarta.
So I'll give you a tour of that later.
Stick around for that.
The weather, these clouds are not looking so good.
But I think we're going to be okay.
I don't think it's going to rain just yet.
Man, the streets are really noisy.
We've got a nice monument there.
A man and a woman holding flowers.
I don't think that is the national monument.
We're still heading in the direction of the national monument.
I think they're doing it continues.
I've just popped into a mall now to grab a bit of the AC.
That's one of the best things about the shopping malls
that you can just utilize.
The lovely, cool AC.
I must say this is quite a luxurious shopping mall.
It's got all the high-end luxury brands.
I'm feeling like Jakarta is a very can of luxurious city.
You have extreme luxury in some places.
And then extreme poverty in other places.
Oh my god, it is luxury.
They've got a Rishad Mew store.
Should we just pop in and get a Rishad Mew?
A Rishad Mewli costs as much as a house.
Where a house on your wrist.
That is mental.
Who blow?
Don't I like who blow?
Omega, not bad.
James Bond wears the no-mega.
You know the king of luxury watches.
His Rolex.
You're going to buy a luxury watch.
I would say by a Rolex.
Let's get out of this mall.
Let's get back on the streets.
The mission is not over.
Let's get out of here.
Bandaran, I, Astra.
I think that's probably the station I should have got off at.
I don't like if I'm just, I could have just stayed on the train.
I just checked on Google Maps.
I keep walking this way.
It'll take me like 28 minutes and we'll be at the monuments.
So, all swell and swell.
Everything turned alright in the end.
Man, there's so many grab and go-jek drivers just waiting here for a ride.
I have the grab app.
I'm ready to use it if necessary.
That's a backup.
If we get extremely lost.
We can just hop on one of these grab bikes which are really convenient.
Actually, just took with around the city.
A Louis Vuitton store there.
There's quite a lot of high-end luxury shopping malls.
Just everywhere you go.
That's another thing that I've found.
And so far, the rain is still holding off.
It's a lucky day, even though the monument's closed.
Maybe they'll magically open it today.
Who knows?
The journey continues.
Another thing I'm noticing about Jakarta is that they have square trees.
Oh my god, look at this in the background.
So more skyscrapers just going up.
Adding to Jakarta's skyline.
Man, there's just shiny buildings everywhere.
It's bedazzling me.
I was just walking there.
That guy behind me said I cannot film.
Don't point my camera in that direction.
Which you can see there's a Japanese flag there.
I'm guessing that's the Japanese embassy.
Maybe things I'm a spy.
I don't know what's going off there, but the man these bikes are so loud.
I guess he didn't know how to film embassies.
I mean, I was just filming the tree.
I was only interested in the square tree.
Can you let me off?
Here's another kind of Minecraft building over there.
We've got some young workers here.
The backbone of the city.
Building there the ones who are doing all the construction.
Hello.
Doing all the work.
Constructing this mega city from the ground up.
Man, the traffic is in full effect.
It's actually probably quicker to walk.
No, the quickest is the bikes, the graph bikes.
Because they can weave in an hour of all the traffic.
Another station there, NHR rim, fam rim.
I don't know if you've announced that.
I'm guessing I could have literally just stayed on the train instead of walking.
I'm literally walking right alongside the tracks.
Anyway, walking is healthier.
We get to breathe in the fresh air of Jakarta.
I mean, it doesn't seem that bad.
Right, so it's healthier to walk anyway.
We're burning lots of calories, making room for the lovely Indonesian food I'm going to be trying.
So I've just checked my Google Maps and I'm about 18 minutes away from the monument.
Well, what's this?
Is this some kind of political bananas?
Oh, it's a McDonald's thing.
One day if they have a kind of special Indonesian McDonald's burger.
Oh, and I just saw over there is a burger king and a Pohai's chicken.
Oh, they've got 3D screen up there.
I think we're getting pretty close now.
We're getting real close.
You see quite a mix of different people on the streets.
And I just found out that Indonesia is a majority Muslim country with over 80% of the people.
Oh, I must have.
But you do see quite a varied mix of different kind of people.
Like East Asian, Indian, Chinese.
I didn't see that many foreigners.
I saw a few of the old kind of banking kind of old men foreigners.
I didn't see many young foreigners around.
Anyway, well, hello.
Lots of friendly people.
I did see that.
What's this?
Please, please bike.
There's lots of action going off everywhere you look.
It's non-stop action.
Mokka coffee to go.
I'm actually getting quite a bit peckish now.
I'm not eating.
I'm not eating the whole day.
And it is now 4.20.
So I could do with shoving some kind of food in my mouth.
Oh my God, I have arrived.
I have arrived.
There it is in front of me.
My journey.
It's closed.
It's closed Monday.
Yeah.
Four o'clock.
England.
You okay?
It's closed and this looks like the exit.
So it is indeed closed.
But at least we've got a glimpse of it.
And also I believe that you can go to the top of it.
I think I'm at the wrong side as well.
I reckon just sneaking through the doors.
Ah, there's no chance.
Ah, anyway, at least we've got a glimpse of it.
I think we'll come back on another day and try and get to the top of it.
Man, look at all this poor wire.
I guess it's trying to stop people from sneaking in.
Let's try and head around this way.
I've also heard that there's a very famous mosque.
We have a new mission acquired.
To the mosque.
Let's see if we can see it.
Which way?
Man, there's so much barbed wire.
Better watch out, I might get tangled up in it.
And there is no...
There is no path.
Where am I supposed to go?
Okay, we're going on the road.
Let's keep on the bridge above.
Watch out.
And getting the feeling that it's quite difficult to walk around Jakarta.
And it's probably better just to get one of these bikes or a taxi or something.
I've just walked around to the front gate.
And so it is closed on a Monday.
Do it a thought.
Guess we'll have to come back on another day.
Good afternoon from the unexpectedly sunny Jakarta.
Look at that blue sky.
I don't know what people are talking about with the...
With the smartness, look at that clear blue sky is here.
Look at that indonesia city of around 11 million people.
Man, the weather is just lovely today.
This is... I've been in Jakarta.
This is the sixth day.
And there's just been no sun.
We're not even seeing the sun.
And now, look at this.
The heat is intense, but I like it.
I like the intense heat.
Man, this is beautiful.
Look at all this kind of...
I don't know what trees there.
If anyone knows, tell me in the comments below.
Oh, and those trees are beautiful as well.
Man, this is really a nice area.
And there it is.
Let's get closer to the monument.
And the sun is shining and the sun is shining.
And the sun is shining.
Oh man, this heat is intense.
I've just...
Right, I don't know what's going on.
I've just done a full lap around.
And there's no way in.
How do you get in?
I'm guessing there's some kind of underground passage.
Oh man, this heat.
I feel like I'm in Sahara Desert.
It's intense.
How do you get in?
All right, next to it.
Hold on.
Oh, entrance.
So the entrance.
It's a little bit confusing.
The entrance is this way.
See, walk away from...
Ah, it is underground.
Ah, the guy is waving.
Ah, that makes sense.
Underground entrance.
Heading underground now.
And I believe this is where you get your ticket.
Wow.
Oh, it's a get into the shade.
Ah, I get tickets here.
Wow, underground passage.
You number from the top.
Okay.
What's that?
What's the access?
Okay.
Thank you.
Sorry about that, you're from England.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Okay, got my ticket.
It cost me...
It cost me 45,000.
And I've also got a number.
A waiting number to go to the top.
I'm number 20.
Right, so...
We're going inside now.
It's kind of like walking in an underground bunker.
I'm getting excited now.
I wonder how you go to the top.
I wonder if they have little stairs that you can take.
Back...
Back into the intense heat.
Woo!
Can't see anything.
Where am I?
Oh, my God.
I mean, side there it is.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, it's huge.
Oh, I see lights.
I see lights at the end of the tunnel.
Wow.
I guess all these people...
They're also waiting to go to the top.
Man, there must be a big queue.
Oh.
One to 35.
Oh, I guess that's me.
So I'm in the next...
I'm in the next batch of people to go in.
Oh, you can go in there.
So sweaty.
And sweaty.
Nice view, though.
Where the view at the top is great.
How about you?
You want a photo?
He doesn't want a photo.
Okay, okay.
There's some guys once take a photo.
They don't see many foreign faces.
So it seems like it says Cessie 4, that is group 4, but my ticket is Cessie Wack 25.
So it looks like I'm still waiting.
I've been here about 10 minutes.
It's still pretty hot even though you're standing in the shade.
But I like the intense heat.
So I prefer to stand in the sun.
Just to feel the intenseness of it.
Just to try and feel something.
Still waiting.
Still waiting to go in.
As you can see, there's quite a lot of people also in group number five.
I don't know how long it's going to be.
It's not too long.
I will continue to stand in the sun until it's my turn.
It's been about 20 minutes now.
Still waiting.
I can't imagine, because it doesn't look that busy.
I can't imagine how long it's going to be waiting.
It's been 20 minutes.
That's the focus worth it.
It's a board mode number.
I think I have a chance of going in, Raelas to see if I can get in.
How much is it?
$5,000.
$5,000?
$2,000.
$5,000.
Okay.
Just one.
Thank you.
Okay.
We're heading to the lift now.
Thank you.
Wow.
It's total weightiness.
It's 30 minutes.
Not bad.
30 minutes.
I can't imagine.
When it's busy, how long you're going to be waiting?
Because I didn't think it's that busy.
There's 132 meters tall.
Still waiting to get into the lift now.
Total weighting time.
40 minutes.
I almost made it in the weight limit.
There's a 800 kilogram weight limit.
Man, that is...
It's now been one hour.
One hour of weighting time.
Man, I'm next.
Surely I'm next to lift.
It's right here.
Oh man.
It's so long.
Oh my god.
I mean, oh my god.
Roll...
Roll crammed in.
Like sardines.
The lift can't actually take that many people.
They need to upgrade the lift.
Because the amount of people that are coming in,
the lift can't handle it.
Some weight in like an hour.
Oh, nice and light.
Freedom.
Oh my god.
Wow.
It is a pretty good view though.
Man, you can see across the entire city of Jakarta.
What is it worth the one hour weight?
Let's take a quick look around.
Was it worth it?
I would say it was not worth the one hour weight.
Oh man.
A one hour weight.
And then I spent like three minutes looking around.
And then I then I also had to queue to get down again.
Oh man.
Is it worth it?
Well, I guess if you really want to see that view then it's worth it.
But with such a long weighting time,
a lot of people taking a picture.
A long weighting time.
Maybe if it was 10 minute weighting time then it's not so bad.
There's another building over there.
It looks like some kind of palace.
But you can't even get close to it.
You can't even cross the road.
And guess what that might be?
Is that the president's house?
Is that the Indonesian White House?
Actually, I don't know.
Do they have a royal family in Indonesia?
I'm pretty sure they have a president.
But do they also have a royal family?
If anyone knows, then tell me in the comments below.
I'm also not sure what this building is.
So if anyone knows, then tell me in the comments below.
You can see the Indonesian flag there flying high.
It's got a lot of security on the building as well.
Oh my god, there's a huge cannon there.
Oh my god, look at that.
Where are they planning on firing to?
Well, you can see them there.
Wow.
Am I heading the right direction?
Where am I going?
I'm trying to find a mosque.
Is it this way?
I just realized sometimes I'm wearing shorts.
So even if there is a kind of tall little toy you can do of the mosque,
I don't think I'm able to get in.
Because I'm wearing shorts.
Anyway, we'll just try and get a glimpse of the mosque.
A bus station there.
Some kind of little street stores.
Street foods, I've got any food here, I'm really hungry.
What was this?
Ah, some kind of souvenirs.
I see a lot of cars with a little blue light on.
They look like they're some kind of government cars or something.
I can get a...
took, took.
Ah, that's the mosque.
And it doesn't look like you can even go inside.
Okay, so that is place number two.
And we couldn't get inside, we could just stand at a gate.
But then must, maybe this is the exit.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on, I'm not giving up just yet.
Maybe that's the exit.
I mean, I don't know if I can even get in anyway.
If you fail to prepare, then prepare to fail.
The journey continues.
Oh, so you can go in.
Hello, can you look at the mosque?
Oh, so we need to serve for the seat to close.
Close for visit?
Tomorrow is open.
Yes, and 10 o'clock until 15.
10 until 3.
Ah, okay.
Just pick 3 again.
And 10 till 3.
Okay, and can wear shorts or no?
Oh, it's no problem.
Because this...
You have something to wear?
Yes.
Ah, okay, okay.
So tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, you're welcome.
Okay, that lovely young man just told me tomorrow.
So we're going to come back tomorrow for the mosque and for the monument.
Oh, I just acquired a new quest.
There's a cathedral nearby.
Let's go check it out.
Surely the cathedral won't let us down.
The journey continues on to the cathedral.
Let's go!
And there she is.
Right, let's try and cross this road without getting run over and see if we can get inside.
Man, okay, okay, okay.
Hold, hold, hold, hold, hold, hold, hold.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, okay.
Okay, we made it.
I made it.
I'm alive.
I'm safe and well.
Can we go inside?
It looks like we can go inside.
Wow.
She is a real beauty.
You wouldn't really expect to see a kind of cathedral like this in Asia.
Let's find out what kind of cathedral is it?
Not too sure if you can go in or not.
I'm just kind of following these people.
It does look pretty nice.
Oh my god.
Oh, this is amazing.
I'm starting to feel quite religious now.
I feel I feel blessed now.
I don't know what kind of cathedral is it.
I mean, I know it's Christianity, but what kind?
Now, how do I get home?
Is that Jesus just chilling out there?
I get it, it must be because it's got a hole in the foot from the old crucifixion.
Right, anyway, back on the streets.
Back out to the streets of Jakarta.
Jakarta.
And the rain has still held off.
I cannot believe it.
This grey cloud has been looming the entire video.
That is pretty nice.
It's pretty, it's pretty, what's the word I'm looking for?
It's pretty breathtaking, spiritual.
When you go inside, you get that kind of feeling, the spiritual feeling.
Now, it's suddenly gotten really dark, so now is a good time to leave.
I've ordered a trusty little grab bite.
And we're going back to my hotel now.
The FAMON Jakarta.
So we'll give you a little tour of the hotel.
It's a pretty nice hotel.
Just waiting on the bike now.
Let's go.
Oh, yeah, it's me.
Okay, let's get on the bike.
Help me.
Help me on first, safety first.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay, I'm ready to go.
They're actually really good getting these grab bites, because you get this kind of free tour around the city.
There's a vibe to the people there.
And they're really good at just weaving in and out through all the traffic.
This young man is very skilled on his bike.
There's the mask on that side.
And here's the streets on this side.
The hustling of the cross-lit streets of Jakarta.
And no way it's like a mad race for all these grab bites and go check bites.
And now I'm enjoying it.
I've become one with Jakarta's traffic.
There's another nice building there.
It looks very presidential.
I think I picked one of the worst times to get a bite back.
I think it's a rush hour.
It's like 5-6 pm.
Oh my god, look at this.
Or you can see across all the city there.
There's a thick, small in the end.
I think I'm slightly greening some of that in right now.
But it's all car views here.
I'm going to have a look at the street.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, we have arrived back at the famed month.
Hello.
We have quite tight security everywhere.
There you go.
Oh yeah, phone.
Oh yeah, I'm here.
Okay, I'm inside.
Quite tight on the security.
This is the lobby.
Oh man, that was such a long journey.
I wasn't expecting it to be that long.
Anyway, let's rate our driver guy.
Let's give him a little tip.
Give him a tip more than the price of the entire ride.
You know, it deserves it.
Working hard, especially on a distance that long.
Anyway, right, up to the room.
These are the corridors.
It is quite a pricey hotel.
The room that we are in, 1624 there, is the card.
A swipe to get in.
This room costs about $300 per night.
You've got a little toilet by the door.
An extra toilet.
Nice little dining table.
Huge living room.
It's a hundred square meters this room.
Around $300 per night with breakfast.
That is super pricey.
You've got a nice view of a golf course.
And the sunset there.
And then the traffic down below.
We actually booked a sky-sweet suite,
which is cheaper than this room.
And that has a kind of little kitchen area.
So this room, although it's bigger and more expensive,
it doesn't have a kitchen thing.
It only just has a fridge.
There's a check inside the fridge here.
You've got all that kind of stuff.
It was all filled in the fridge.
I had to take it out and put it on the side here
to put our stuff in the fridge.
Because obviously, we don't want to be used
paying for a sprite when it costs $40,000.
How much is $40,000?
How many in US dollar?
40,000.
Is it like...
Lost in the digits.
$40,000, that's like $7,000, is it?
If anyone knows how I'm in the commis bill,
and then you come over into the bedroom.
Quite a huge bed.
Good size.
I think it's about two meters width.
Let's do a bed test.
Quite comfortable.
Oh, quite comfortable. Really soft.
I think they've added some kind of extra padding on here.
You've got like a walking wardrobe place.
Iron.
You can just iron things.
Yeah, that's good.
Okay.
Wait, how do I put it back?
Nice big wardrobe with a safe
to put all your gold bars in.
And all your money in.
I don't think I've ever used a hotel safe.
I see some other vloggers
and they put their laptop inside the hotel.
I think they're going to have a room
for the hotel.
I see some other vloggers
and they put their laptop inside the hotel.
Say for me,
who do you think is going to steal their laptop?
I mean, especially in a hotel like this.
I don't think you have to worry about your valuables,
to be honest with you.
Room, room, room, housekeeping.
So I'm going to steal your stuff.
I don't think.
Then over here we've got a lovely massive,
quite a massive bathroom.
Two sinks, his and her sinks.
And then a little makeup mirror.
Listen.
I don't know what's that?
No, if you can hear that, that's the call to prayer.
Bega, use to that in Indonesia.
You'll always hear it.
And then we've got another toilet.
So I should give you a full of two toilets.
This is the first hotel room
that I've been in.
It has two toilets. That's crazy.
And then over here we have a shower
with a rain kind of shower day and the other shower day.
And quite a big bath.
Oh, it's very echoey inside of here.
Okay, it's very echoey.
It's got good acoustics in there.
My head on out.
I hate the used to, in hotels,
do you used to give you loads and little things?
And now they're kind of transferred
and they're just putting in these little
tub-stocking walls.
Got another view there.
Across Jakarta, you can see there's a stadium there,
football stadium, some other kind of stadium.
More traffic.
They got what you're doing?
They got it!
Another view of the golf course
and then the lovely Jakarta traffic below there.
Got a nice little desk area.
Pretty comfy.
Usually you don't get a good desk chair
to sit at your computer.
But this one is pretty good.
Good leg to desk height ratio,
quite comfortable for editing or the video.
Another TV there.
Oh, how many TV are we got?
Two TVs.
Big TV there.
Mirror here.
So you can check yourself out.
Okay.
Did I show everything in this one?
Kouch by the TVs there.
Another TV there.
This couch is actually really comfy as well.
You could also just sleep here if you wanted to.
Okay, I'm going to sleep now.
I don't know if you can see that.
Wait, let's turn on the lights off.
That's a pretty nice sunset.
There's one thing that you would expect to be better
if you press master
that all the lights go off.
But it doesn't.
So anyway, can we see?
Okay.
Wow, look at this.
Oh, that is such a good view.
Is this the beautiful,
beautiful sunset of Jakarta?
Made left a little note, which is quite sweet.
It says,
Dear Mr. Jason Pie.
Don't know why she wrote pie.
Jason Pie.
Why did she write pie?
Oh, it's Rick.
It's Rick.
Oh, that's my middle name, Richard.
But why she wrote Jason Rick?
Anyway, thank you for,
thank you for staying at Fairmont, Jakarta.
We hope you are happy staying with us.
We make this arrival towel for you and we give extra...
extra something capsule.
I mean, all water, we hope you are always happy with us.
And your days are also fun.
Happy good day, Mr. Jason.
Room attendance.
Sonia.
Okay, very sweet kind letter from Sonia.
Thank you for that.
She made like a little towel dinosaur.
But it's already been destroyed now, unfortunately.
They also have bottles of water, which is free.
Free water, kind of similar to in Bangkok, in Thailand hotels.
They also put the water.
Wait.
They also put the water in glass bottles and refill them.
I guess that's some kind of environmental thing.
Okay.
There's some leftovers that I had earlier.
I mean, this is probably one of the best things in Indonesia.
Silver Queen.
Ever since I've had this.
I've been dreaming about getting another one.
This is better than cabbres, better than Mars, better than Galaxy, better than Dove,
better than Oreo, silver Queen.
Should be Silver King.
Is there a silver king?
Maybe someone should make that.
Really good.
10 out of 10.
Chocolate bar.
What's in here?
N.T. wardrobe.
Let's just check inside of here.
Okay, just make sure that everything is safe.
Okay.
Oh, the light's gone off.
Yep.
Everything's okay inside of here.
It's not a box there.
What is that?
There's a mysterious white box in the corner.
It's panasonic.
Oh, is that the modem?
I mean, that's the internet modem.
Anyway, the second toilet.
It's also one of those kind of electric toilets.
I believe that can shoot water directly up your bottom.
If you're into that kind of thing.
Anyway, it's a nice little room tour.
And instead of pressing the button,
like do not disturb, or please make up my room,
they've gone for the old fashioned way of hanging this on the door.
Mahon titak di gannagoo.
So yeah.
I just ordered some nice Indonesian food.
I don't know if you've heard of this dish.
It's called pizza.
A nice Indonesian pizza there.
This one's Hawaiian.
This one's some Milano.
And I also got some,
let's look at this one.
Some garlic bread.
Let's try this Indonesian pizza.
That's pretty good.
8.4 out of 10.
That was a nice little snack.
Now it's time for dessert.
Just a little snack.
Just a few donuts here.
Not too many.
I don't want to have too many.
Just 12 there.
Wait how many is here?
I don't want to have too many.
Let's not forget the milk as well.
Okay, wow, look at this.
Nice little Indonesian snack here.
Cheers.
Wait can you see me?
Hmm.
Oh, oh, hello there.
Just laying on my bed in my room.
Oh wait, no.
I'm at the poolside area.
Let me give you a little tour around here.
Let's do another full hotel tour later.
That's the hotel there.
Got a lovely pool here.
Some lounges that you can come and sunbathe in.
I'll go see it's nighttime now.
So there's no sun.
And actually there is a thunderstorm.
It's got some lightning flash earlier.
Let's see if we can catch any on camera.
I don't know, should you go swimming?
Should you go swimming when it's lightning?
I don't know, I guess the hotel staff would have told us to go back inside.
If they thought we were in danger.
It's slightly a little bit chilly.
Oh, hello.
Okay.
Oh, it's nice there once you're in.
It's really peaceful and relaxing, especially when it's empty.
So yes, I'm not too sure what's the rules when there's lightning.
Because we're on the fourth floor, so we're not that high up.
So I'm guessing the lightning wouldn't strike the water first.
It would strike the top of the building.
If it wasn't that I'd say, let me know.
Should I be getting out of the pool?
Maybe that's why there's no one in the pool.
And just saw a flash.
Hello.
Here we have a nice little jacuzzi.
I don't know if you can see anything because it's so dark.
Let's just get in.
Hold on.
Let me just come to the middle of the jacuzzi because there's a bit of a light here.
Okay, I've got a bit of a light.
Okay, you can see me.
Oh, one of the jets is shooting right up there.
Anyway, that is not the end of the journey.
It continues right here.
Yes, I'm waiting until you click.